[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "type": "multi",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Who wrote the title page of The Book of Mormon?",
    "answer": ["Mormon"],
    "options": ["Joseph Smith", "Mormon", "Moroni"]
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The abridgment of the record is written to the Jew and Gentile.",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The record is written by way of commandment, and also by the spirit of ____ and of revelation.",
    "answer": ["prophecy"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The record was written and sealed up, and hid up unto the Lord, that they may not be destroyed",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Where in the Book of Mormon is the word Lamanites first mentioned?",
    "answer": ["Title Page"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The word “Jaredites” first appears to in the Title page of the Book of Mormon?",
    "answer": ["false"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "An abridgment is taken from the Book of ____, which is a record of the people of Jared.",
    "answer": ["ether"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The people of Jared were scattered at the time the Lord confounded their language.",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "At time the Lord confounded the language of the Jaredites, they were trying to build a ____ to get to heaven.",
    "answer": ["tower"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The Lord has done many great things unto the remnant of the House of ____.",
    "answer": ["Israel"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The Lord wants to show the remnant House of Israel the many great things that he has done for their fathers.",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "type": "multi",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The Lord wants the House of Israel to know the ____ he has made with them and not be cast-off forever.",
    "answer": ["Covenants"],
    "options": ["Bible", "Articles of Faith", "Covenants"]
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "The Lord wants to convince Jews and Gentiles that Jesus is the ____.",
    "answer": ["Christ"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Jesus is the Christ, the Eternal God, manifesting himself unto all nations.",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Mormon states that if there are faults in the record, they are the ____ of Men.",
    "answer": ["Mistakes"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "type": "bool",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Mormon writes, condemn not the things of God?",
    "answer": ["true"],
    "options": ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "type": "fill",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Mormon wants us to be found spotless at the _____ seat of Christ",
    "answer": ["Judgment"],
    "options": ["fill"]
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "type": "multi",
    "ref": "Book of Mormon Title Page",
    "question": "Who translated the title page of the Book of Mormon?",
    "answer": ["Joseph Smith"],
    "options": ["Moroni", "Mormon", "Joseph Smith"]
  }
]
